americastire.com 2018-10-20

# Privacy Policy | America's Tire

America's Tire is committed to the privacy of customer information gathered in retail stores, mobile applications, and online through discounttire.com, americastire.com, and discounttiredirect.com websites (collectively, the “Site”). America's Tire has created this statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of both the customer's information as well as our own. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our Site. 

By using our Site, you agree to the collection, use, and information sharing practices described in this statement of America's Tire's policy. Amendments to this statement will be posted at this URL and will be effective when posted. Your continued use of our Site after the amendments are posted constitutes your agreement to those changes. Please read this statement carefully and check back regularly for any amendments. 

**Information Collected**

We collect personally identifiable information that you voluntarily submit to us, such as information you provide on an order form for tires, wheels, or services, or when you communicate with us on our Site, such as through a Live Chat. The type of information includes, but is not limited to; your contact information (e.g., physical addresses, phone numbers, and email addresses) and financial information (e.g., account numbers). Information about your vehicle(s) may also be collected. We may also collect information from you when you agree to participate in surveys or provide other feedback to us on our Site. We may combine personally identifiable information collected on our Site with other information that we collect in stores, when you call or email us, communicate with us through social media, or from other data sources. 

We also collect non-personally identifiable information about you in a number of ways. Our methods of information collection include tracking your Site activities through your computer settings or most-recently visited URL. We may also ask you to provide certain non-personally identifiable information about yourself, such as your age, household income, buying preferences, etc. 

**Use of Personal Information**

We use your personal information to conduct business, including processing transactions; responding to and fulfilling your requests; for our marketing efforts, such as to send you marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you; for analysis and development of new products and services; to improve the Site; for our legitimate business purposes permitted under the law; and for any other purpose to which you consent. 

**Use of Non-Personal Information**

We use the customer's non-personal information to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Site. The IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information. 

**Use of Cookies and Web Beacons**

When you view our Site we might store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file. Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive, not on our site. Cookies do not spy on you or otherwise invade your privacy, and they cannot invade your hard drive and steal information. They are designed to help you navigate our Site as easily as possible. 

America's Tire uses various third-party advertising technology sources to display ads to customers. In the course of displaying our advertisements to you, a unique third-party cookie may be placed or recognized on your browser. In addition, we use web beacons to help manage our online advertising. These web beacons enable our ad server to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits this site and to learn which ads bring users to our site 

One such third-party services that we utilize is Google Analytics. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. You can learn more about Google’s privacy practices, or adjust your ad settings, by visiting their website at http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/. 

We, and our service providers, use cookies, web beacons, and other technologies to receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us through your computer, tablet or mobile device. This information includes but is not limited to: the pages you visit on our Site or mobile application; the web address from which you came; the type of browser/device/hardware you are using; purchase information and checkout process; search terms; and Internet Protocol-based geographic location. All this helps us recognize you, customize your Site experience and make our marketing messages more relevant. These cookies, web beacons, and any other tracking technologies used on our Site may track users over time and across third-party websites and services. 

We may connect information collected automatically with information we already have about you in order to identify you as a America's Tire guest. If we are able to identify you as a guest we may, for example, link your activity on our Site to your activity in a America's Tire store or on one of our mobile applications. This allows us to provide you with a personalized experience regardless of how you interact with us – online, in store, mobile, etc. 

In order to provide the best guest experience possible, we also use automated information collection technologies for reporting and analytics purposes. We examine metrics such as how you are shopping on our Site, in our stores, and on our mobile applications, the performance of our marketing efforts, and your response to those marketing efforts. 

Our Site does not respond to Internet browser Do Not Track signals. 

**Information Sharing**

We may share your personal information with third parties, such as social media services that we partner with; with anyone to whom you expressly consent; with law enforcement or other entities subject to legal requirements; to protect our rights or the rights or safety of others; with manufacturers for recall and other safety purposes; and as otherwise may be required by law or regulation. We may also share aggregated data about our customers, in a non-personally identifiable form, to non-affiliated companies for certain purposes, such as market research, safety, data modeling, and analytics. 

We also share personal information with our third party service providers. We require that our service providers only use shared personal information to perform the services requested by America's Tire in accordance with this privacy statement and that the service providers have adequate security measures in place to protect any of your shared personal information. 

In the event that we enter into a corporate transaction, such as a reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer, or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets, or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings), we may transfer personal information that we have collected to the relevant third party. 

**Affiliate Site's Privacy Policies**

The Synchrony Car Care credit application form is managed and maintained by Synchrony Financial. Any and all data collected by Synchrony Financial is governed by the privacy policy of Synchrony Financial and not America's Tire. [ Synchrony Bank’s Privacy Policy](https://ch04.rfecom.com/dualcardimages/dualcard/gemoney/en/html/InternetPrivacyPolicy.html)

Our eBay sales are managed by eBay.com. Any and all data collected from these orders will be governed by the privacy policies of eBay.com and not America's Tire. [ eBay Privacy Policy](http://pages.ebay.com/help/policies/privacy-policy.html)

**Other Websites and Links**

This Site contains links and references to other sites, including social media, but America's Tire is in no way responsible for the privacy practices, security measures, or the content of such websites. 

**Security**

This Site utilizes reasonable security measures and technologies to prevent the loss, misuse, or alteration of the information under our control. Although we are committed to protecting the privacy of your information, please do your part to protect your information by keeping your software patched, using updated anti-virus or anti-malware software, using personal firewalls, and an updated unique complex password. 

**Choice and Opt Out**

You may opt-out of receiving communications from our partners and from us by sending an email to consumeraffairs@discounttire.com with “Opt out” in the subject line. 

**Children’s Privacy**

This Site is not intended for persons under the age of 18 years. We do not knowingly collect, maintain, or use personal information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that a child under the age of 13 has submitted personal information to us through the Site, we will immediately delete such information. 

**Contacting Our Administrators**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, you can contact us at:
